&gt；&gt；steve kinney：那么让我们回去做一些更多的实验。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So let's go back and
let's do a few more experiments.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：让我们看看，我有一个名为Classes的类，看起来很有用。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Let's take a look, I have
one called classes, that seems useful.
所以你可以看到我们隐藏了另一个这样的东西
And so you can see we have
another one of these hidden
VA特殊函数，这个函数叫做HaveSameMap。
VA special functions, and
this one is called HaveSameMap.
对，就是它们有相同的形状吗？
Right, which is,
do they have the same shape?
他们两个是单形的，对吗？
Are the two of them monomorphic, right?
所以，让我们继续，让我们尝试一下这段代码。
So let's go ahead and let's try this code.
所以如果我不使用Allow-Native-语法，它就会崩溃。
And so it will crash if I don't use
that allow-natives-syntax thing.
所以我会说node，&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：allow-local-语法
So I'll say node,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: allow-natives-syntax
说classes.js，我是如何得到false的？
Say classes.js And how did I get false?
这就说得通了，其中一个有a属性，一个有b属性，
Which makes sense, one of them has an a
property, one of them has a b property,
它们是不一样的。
they are not the same.
好吧，酷，如果它们是一样的呢？
All right cool,
what if they were the same?
是的，好吧，就像他们在这个世界上的理智一样，
True, all right,
like their sanity in the world,
我们知道一切都会好起来的。
we know that everything is gonna be okay.
好吧，那么价值重要吗？
All right, so does the value matter?
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：让我们来看看。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Let's check it out.
对，这个价值显然让它有所不同，但是
Right, that value clearly made
it something different but
这是一个相当大的数字。
that's a pretty large number.
让我们使用一个更像公平的数字。
Let's use use a more like fair number.
现在是真的了。
Now it's true.
我现在就会毁了那一个
I will spoil that one now just so
在我稍后解释之前，你不必活在你心中挥之不去的疑虑中。
you don't have to live with that lingering
doubt in you until I explain it later.
也就是说，在传递一个32位整数后，它不再是相同的小数字了。
Which is, after you pass a 32 bit integer,
it's not the same small number anymore.
就像，在一定的尺寸之后，它们是不同的类型。
Like, after a certain size,
they are a different type.
对，但如果你保持，如果你低于32位数字，
Right, but if you keep,
if you're under a 32 bit number like,
如果你保持你的数字小，他们是相同的类型。
if you keep your numbers small,
they are the same type.
我们将看一个小图表，稍后会有一大堆意义。
We'll look at a little chart and
it'll make a bunch of sense later.
但是，是的，所以一般说来，价值必须是相同的，
But, yeah, so generally speaking,
the values have to be the same,
很明显，如果这是一个字符串，我们可以预期是假的，对吗？
clearly if this was a string,
we can expect false, right?
所以，中心有一个很长的数字，但是
So, the center with a very long number but
在正常数字的范围内，比如五万，这是真的，对吗？
in the range of normal numbers like
five 50,000, it's true, right?
他们是一样的。
They're the same.
好的，酷。
All right, cool.
如果我们把这个像x属性一样给它会发生什么呢？
What happens if we give
this one like a x property?
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：假的，对吗？
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: False, right?
它们不一样。
They're not the same.
他们不再有相同的形状了。
They don't have the same shape anymore.
其中一个有x属性，另一个没有，对吧？
One of them has an x property,
one of the doesn't, right?
所以看起来V8在某种程度上一直在跟踪这个很酷的东西。
So it seems like V8 has in some way
that it's keeping track of this cool.
如果他们也有一样的呢？
What if they had the same?
所以给定X，A和X。
So given X, an A and an X.
[噪音]好的
[NOISE]
Okay.
没错，这就是我们所期望的。
True that's what we would expect.
它们具有相同的属性。
They have the same properties.
它们是相同的价值观，对吗？
They are the same values right?
是世界上某种程度上的理智。
Is some amount of sanity in the world.
但是发生了什么，让我们去同一个地方。
But what happens,
let's get to the same place.
所以第一个将有一个A和一个X，第二个将有一个A。
So the first one is gonna have an A and
an X, the second one is gonna have an A.
我们将为其添加一个X。
We'll add an X to it.
所以应该是一回事，对吗？
So that should be the same thing right?
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：不是。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: It's not.
很有趣，所以如果他们开始的时候一样，
Interesting, so if they start the same,
如果我做的方式完全一样，它们也是一样的。
if I'm making the exact same way,
they're the same.
但如果我以不同的方式开始，他们的结局就不一样了，有趣。
But if I start differently,
they don't end up the same, interesting.
如果我做同样的事情，
What happens if I do the same thing,
就像如果我继续说像S[声音]，
like what if I go ahead and
say like S [SOUND],
他们走的是同一条路。
they follow the same path.
因此，我们将它们的x属性都设置为Numbers。
So, we’ll set the x property
on both them to numbers.
他们一开始就只是一个A级的财产。
They’ll start out as just an A property.
我们将在他们两个上设置一个x属性，对吗？
We’ll set an x property on both of them,
right?
现在他们又回到了地图上。
Now they’re the same the map again.
好的，所以他们开始一样，他们开始不同
Okay so they start the same the same,
they start different and
结果是一样的，他们是不一样的。
end up the same they are not the same.
但如果他们一起走过相同的道路，他们就是一样的。
But if they go through the same
path together, they are the same.
好吧，我还不明白这是怎么回事，但我只是在做一些科学研究。
Okay, I don't understand how this works
yet, but I'm just doing some science.
好的，我们再做一件事
All right we'll one more thing
我们将从这个a开始，我们将使用我们的好朋友对象out赋值。
We'll start out with this a and we'll
use our good friend object out assign.
Object Out Assign用于制作对象。
Object out assign is used for
making objects.
我们要做的就是拿a，然后复制它，对吗？
And what we'll do is we'll just take
the a and we'll copy it, right?
如果您想要保持不可变的数据结构和
If you ever want to keep
immutable data structures and
反应你可以使用对象输出分配。
react you can use object out assign.
或者如果你曾经使用过扩散运算符，比如这三个点，
Or if you ever used a spread operator,
like those three dots,
那是为了战斗它分配的对象。
that's to battle it's
object that assigned.
它对于克隆对象很有用，对吧？
It's a useful for cloning objects, right?
假的，那不是克隆人吗？
False, isn't that a clone?
我想是因为我们从这个物体开始
I guess because we started
with this object and
然后我们添加了所有的属性，它走了一条不同的道路。
then we added all the properties,
it went down a different path.
这就是我猜的，我们走着瞧。
That's what I'm guessing, we'll see.
好吧，但是如果康斯特
All right, But what happens if did const
C，&GT；&GT；史蒂夫·金尼：我们会看到B和
c,
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: And we'll see are b and
一样吗？
c the same?
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：它们是，因为它们是以相同的方式创建的，对吗？
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: They are, cuz they
were created in the same way, right?
所以这里有一些关于它是如何被创造的东西，
So there's something
about how it was created,
它在修改时所经过的路径。
the path that it went
down as it was modified.
属性以相同的顺序添加。
The properties are added
in the same order.
看起来他们确实有同样的地图。
It seems like they do have the same map.
最终相同但它们以不同的顺序放置在那里的属性，
The properties that end up the same but
they are put there in a different order,
看起来他们没有相同的地图。
seems like they don't have the same map.
对，我们还没有弄清楚为什么会发生这样的事情。
Right, we don't have the words to
figure out why this is happening yet.
但我们绝对是在经验上注意到了一些事情。
But we're definitely
empirically noticing things.
好了，不要再玩对象分配的把戏了。
All right,
No more tricks with object assignment.
我给你看一个应该很直接的。
I'll just show you one that should
be pretty straight forward.
我们将从以前做我们的点类。
We'll make our point class from before.
&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：this.x-x；this.y=y；非常酷。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: This.x-
x; this.y=y; Very cool.
我们会说A是新的
And we'll say A is new
1.2分，
Point 1.2,
B是新的点，我们会幸运地猜一猜。
and B is new Point, and
we'll take a lucky guess.
这些会是一样的吗？
Are these gonna be the same?
你们不必马上回答。
You don't all have to answer at once.
&gt；&gt；steve kinney：幸运的猜测。
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: Lucky guesses.
我看到你在点头。
I see nodding.
我要把点头当作一样，我听到的也是一样。
I'm gonna take the nodding as same,
I heard a same.
我们准备好了，我们投票决定了整个房间都是一样的。
We're ready,
we've voted this entire room same.
我们赢了对吧？
We win, right?
是的，它们的构造方式相同，它们通过构造函数。
Yeah, they're constructed the same way,
they go through a constructor.
酷吧？
Cool, right?
所以它看起来像是开始于相同或
So it looks like objects that
either start the same or
经历相同的制作过程，而不是相同的。
go through the same process of
being made and not be the same.
即使他们以同样的方式结束，他们也走过了一条不同的道路。
Even if they end up the same they
went through a different path.
就像V8似乎并不相信它们是同一个对象。
Like V8 doesn't seem to believe
they are the same object.
这是一种有趣的，酷的。
Which is kind of interesting, cool.
如果我们将其中一个属性设置为未定义，
And if we were to set one of
these properties to undefined,
喜欢同样的东西。
like the same thing.
他们将不再拥有[INAUDIBLE]。
They would no longer have the [INAUDIBLE].
你修改这两个中的任何一个，它们最终都不会有相同的地图。
You modify either one of these they
end up not having the same map.
来来回回对吧？
Back and forth, right?
但是如果你对他们两个做同样的事情，他们就会，对吗？
But if you were to do the same thing
to both of them, they do, right?
我们可以通过那个，我会让你免于死亡的进军
We could go through that,
I'll spare you the march of death
通过我们所看到的一切的各种组合。
through every kind of combination
of everything that we've seen.
好吧，这真的很有趣。
Okay, that's really interesting.
要是我们知道发生了什么就好了。
If only we knew what was happening.